{
    "subject": "resource/The_Pleasure_of_His_Company",
    "predicate": "ontology/writer",
    "object": "resource/Cornelia_Otis_Skinner",
    "human_readable": "The writer of 'The Pleasure of His Company' is Cornelia Otis Skinner.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9085040092468262,
            "question": "Who wrote 'The Pleasure of His Company'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9005706906318665,
            "question": "Who was Cornelia Otis Skinner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8193385601043701,
            "question": "What is the title of Cornelia Otis Skinner's book?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7464244961738586,
            "question": "Is 'The Pleasure of His Company' a novel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7007998824119568,
            "question": "Can you name another work by Cornelia Otis Skinner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6840255856513977,
            "question": "Who are some characters in 'The Pleasure of His Company'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6059841513633728,
            "question": "When was 'The Pleasure of His Company' published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5109243392944336,
            "question": "What is the main theme of 'The Pleasure of His Company'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48577597737312317,
            "question": "What makes 'The Pleasure of His Company' a popular book?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.441500186920166,
            "question": "What genre does 'The Pleasure of His Company' likely belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The writer of 'The Pleasure of His Company' is Cornelia Otis Skinner.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3932_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes 'The Pleasure of His Company' a popular book?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3932_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main theme of 'The Pleasure of His Company'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3932_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'The Pleasure of His Company' published?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3932_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3932_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3932_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3932_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3932_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3932_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3932_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3932_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3932_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3932_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3932_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** According to the provided context, it is clear that \"The Pleasure of His Company\" was a play co-authored by Samuel Taylor and Cornelia Otis Skinner. Therefore, the statement \"The writer of 'The Pleasure of His Company' is Cornelia Otis Skinner\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}